# Mohamed Magdy Nour El-Dien

Egypt, Cairo Ain-shams 01061152850 | mm9276285@gmail.com

## **Resume Summary**

I'm Mohamed Magdy, I'm 23 years old, born in cairo Egypt, I'm a junior React.JS Developer I
have more than three years experience with coding as a Computer Science with developing and
implementing user interface design and components using react.js web application and Im good
with monitoring and improving front-end performance testing and debugging application code and
I have troubleshooting and project management skills, Im olso always try to be aware of
documenting application changes and developing updates.

I am in the last year of faculty of computer sience . And my goal that if i was accepted in a good jop i will postpone this year because i want to put my experience in coding as a frontend developer , and i am confident that i can be a valuable asset to any web development team .

## **Experience**

• Portfolio wepsite 07/2023 - 08/2023

link: https://mohamed482000.github.io/portfolio/ GitHub: https://github.com/mohamed482000/portfolio

CRUD using JavaScript

11/2022 - 12/2022

link: https://mohamed482000.github.io/product-management-system-crud/ GitHub: https://github.com/mohamed482000/product-management-system-crud/

Responsive shopping cart using React-JS

09/2023 - 10/2023

shopping cart with admin dashboard use context api to store data come from render website that alternative to json server

link: https://shopping-cart-rosy-ten.vercel.app

GitHub: https://github.com/mohamed482000/shopping-cart

Responsive book store using React-JS

08/2023 - 09/2023

link: https://shopping-cart-react-bice.vercel.app/

GitHub: https://github.com/mohamed482000/shopping-cart-react

#### Education

Helwan university
 Computer Science

### **Skills**

- Html , CSS , JavaScript
- JavaScript framework (React JS)
- React workflows ( Redux , Redux Toolkit , webpack )
- Bootstrap, react-Bootstrap, tailwind css, Material UI
- information technology
- Basics of Data structure, algorithm

## Languages

Arabic - English